The PMO group, the PMO Media group are rock stars. They took the Ekabo Home
Realty team from like a hundred followers to over 1,500 in less than 12
months. It was pretty incredible to see the new content getting pumped out.
I'm somebody that's pretty busy, so there's times where I wouldn't have the
material to even put into the folder for editing, but they found creative ways
to still stay aligned with our goals and to find more stuff — whether it was from
podcasts that I did, or whether it was from creating this AI cartoon that
looked kind of similar to me and was delivering on the messages that we
deliver on: being investor-friendly realtors. So I'd highly recommend, for
anybody who's looking for a social media manager, to give these guys a shot. They
crushed it for us and continue to.